FRONT-END DEVELOPER · WEB SUPPORT

□+1 (951) 232-0215 | ☑ jarrel.thomas@gmail.com | 🐐 | ☑ Organic-Species | 🛅 jarrel-thomas

"The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time."

Summary.

Highly skilled Wordpress Developer with 4+ years of experience specializing in the frontend development, site management, and modern frameworks. Super nerd who loves geeking out on web design and development and exploring new environments. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

- · www.rccoc.org/
- www.sra.mn/

Education

B.S. in Computer Information Systems FIT(Florida Institute of Technology) Melbourne, Florida 2017 - 2021

Work Experience _

TwilioAtlanta, GA

TECHNICAL SUPPORT ENGINEER

Jun. 2021 - Present

- Support global customer base from small business to enterprise-level for Twilio SendGrid's email communication platform and API across multiple mediums (email, Zendesk, phone).
- Regularly meet or exceeded monthly productivity goals of 500 cases via email ticket, phone calls, live chats and social media outreach while maintaining a high level of customer satisfaction.
- · Host team-wide trainings in addition to mentoring new team members to create a higher-level knowledge base of support team.
- Maintain subject matter expertise in Twilio SendGrid SMTP/Web API integration, email deliverability, domain authentication, and IP reputation.

City of Redlands Redlands, CA

DESKTOP SUPPORT SPECIALIST

Jul. 2019 - Jun. 2021

- Improved technological work environments though rapidly diagnosing, troubleshooting and resolving user issues; praised by users and head
 of departments.
- Managed user account information including rights, security, and system groups...
- Dispatched city-wide analyst, installation, and integration of mobile computer infrastructures in Redlands Police Department motorized vehicles

Santa Rosa Academy Menifee, CA

TIER 2 SUPPORT TECHNICIAN

Oct. 2018 - Jul. 2019

- Managed Academy Wordpress website by updating layout design and maintaining backend, in addition to publishing, updating, and managing site content
- Designed and deployed school's newsletters and promotional emails for over 500+ families and staff.
- Consolidated and maintain reports and dashboards of student data to offer insights on academic statistics and student registrations.
- Discuss technical solutions with clients and provide innovative new ideas and solutions.

RDO Equipment Co. Riverside, CA

TRAFFIC COORDINATOR

Mar. 2016 - Oct. 2018

- Utilize RDO computer applications (S2 trafficking systems) to monitor equipment movement and digitally assign inventory to designated customers
- Improved customer satisfaction rate by 45% by implementing mobile device technologies to increase productivity.

Lure Solutions, LLC Rancho Cucamonga, CA

WEBSITE SUPPORT ADMINISTRATOR

Jan. 2018 - Apr. 2018

- Designed and developed more than 50 client websites with WordPress.
- Provided senior technical support to customers on WordPress related issues.
- Redesigned customers HTML and CSS code to fit their brand company brand

Honors & Awards

2021 **Finalist**, MLH Top 50 Class of 2021

U.S.A

2020 **Champion**, Chef Software Project Award

Seattle, Washington